What is it?
Sound the alarm
Enemy attack
Alert the Guild Lord, now
What is that?
Get down!
Take cover!
Run!
Xiaoyu!
Let's move!
Speak
Who sent you here?
It's you!
a
o
Um
Xiaohei
Shifu
There's a new mission
Get ready
We'll be on our way soon
Where to this time?
The Headquarter
Sounds fun
I've never been there before
Lord Wuxian
I need to use the Portal
Of course. Please follow me
Wuxian
On a mission?
Lord Wuxian
Good to see you
Who's that?
He's the most powerful Enforcer
in the entire Yao Ling Guild
That's him
He is a Human, like us
Shifu
So many Humans here
I thought you said we shouldn't let
Humans know about Spirits
These Humans work here
The Guild trusts them
Do they have Ling Power too?
A few do
But most are just ordinary people
You'll see more at the Headquarter
Anything I can help you with?
I'm good, thanks
Then I wish you a pleasant journey
Cang Nan Guild
This place is huge
This is the first Portal
in Yao Ling Guild history
It was built over a thousand years ago
Let's go
Shifu, come on
Shifu
So that's the legendary Wuxian
Finally get to see him in person
He doesn't look as strong as I imagined
Is that his new disciple?
Seems his main mission these days is...
Babysitting
The title of the most powerful Enforcer
should be yours now, Shifu
Be careful what you say
Don't be rude to your seniors
Sorry
Shifu
So this is the junior brother, my Shidi
Right
I thought I was your Last Disciple?
Well... he is...
My Very Last Disciple
Meet your senior sister Luye
Shijie
Let's go
Everyone is waiting for you
Wuxian
You're finally here
Lingyao
Long time no see
You're the one to talk
Is that him?
Xiaohei, right?
Nice to meet you
Such a cute one
Alright, everyone's waiting
Let's go
The Elders
Lord Wuxian
Wuxian
Guild Lord
That's Nezha
This mission must be important
Even Lord Nezha is here
Well, pretend I'm not...
What's this special mission?
You
Really have no idea?
You don't know what
happened at Liu Shi Guild?
They were brutally attacked
And the Ruomu Wood was already stolen
All Spirits there were killed...
Including the head of
Liu Shi Guild, Lord Dasong
Dasong
He was a powerful one
There were traces of all
kinds of firearms at the scene
We believe the attackers were
Humans
Liu Shi Guild is quite formidable
And they didn't receive any
warning when they were attacked?
Here, a bullet shell from the scene
The bullet tip
Was inlaid with Ruomu Wood
Ruomu Wood?
The Ruomu Wood comes
from the sacred Ruomu Tree
Except for a tiny amount that was cut
and lost a long time ago
All that's available was
kept safe at Liu Shi Guild
The Ruomu Wood is harder than iron
It contains Ling Power
Which is harmeless on its own
But Humans exploited its unique properties
and used it to make bullets
So you're saying
Humans obtained materials for weapons
specifically designed against Spirits.
Exactly
They can now produce tens of
millions of bullets using the Ruomu Wood
But human-made bullets
couldn't have taken Dasong down
That's why you had to
do the job yourself, right?
Ling Power Detection doesn't lie
The report from the scene
shows, you led the attack
Me?
I see what's really going on here
And check this out...
Interesting, isn't it?
These crappy human-made
gadgets can actually work a bit
Shifu
Now...
What do you have to say?
To put it simply
Liu Shi Guild was wiped
A large amount of weapons
that can harm Spirit were stolen
And the suspect is me
Correct, that's why we called you back
Good thing you showed
up, there's still room to talk
What's left to talk about?
These days, anything can be faked
And what's in it for
Wuxian? He's got no motive
Of course he does
Isn't he a Human?
Helping humans get their hands
on weapons that could kill Spirits
You don't think that's motive enough?
Let's not jump to conclusions
Are there any other possibilities?
Would any Spirit do something like that?
Who would lead Humans
to wipe out the Spirits?
Besides, Dasong is no ordinary Enforcer
Can you think of anyone who can beat him?
Everyone here can beat him
Then what motive could any of us have
If the Guild Lord doesn't
have the guts to punish Wuxian
Then put him on a public trial
Let all the Spirits be the judges
Nonsense
What, you have the guts?
If the goal of the attack was to pit Humans
and Spirits against each other...
Then I'd be the perfect target
In order to keep me in check
The Guild has to put some
of the best Enforcers on it
And that also ties up those Enforcers
I presume
Lord Nezha came here for me, didn't he?
How do we break out of this dilemma
I can stay at the Headquarter
But if the Ruomu Wood
really is in Human hands
It will spread across the
world before we can blink
Our top priority now
Is to find and retrieve the Ruomu Wood
Don't worry
We're already on it
But all things considered
You are presently
considered a person of interest
I hope you work with us on this matter
Sure, what do you want me to do?
Do you even need to ask?
Put on the Ling Lock
And wait in Icecloud City for your trial
Elder Chi
Why the rush?
Honestly, I'm more suspicious of you
What?
If Lord Wuxian really
wanted to hurt the Guild
Why would he need Ruomu Wood
weapons, or help from Humans?
Or maybe he just wanted to remind you
what Ruomu Wood can be used for?
Don't you know how powerful he is?
And if Lord Wuxian isn't the culprit...
Then the Guild has not
only lost the Ruomu Wood
But also your only lead
And now you want to disable his Ling Power
Who's going to keep him safe?
Both Wuxian and the Guild
could be on the enemy's hit list
Who's ready to take that responsibility?
Luye
What gives you the right to speak here?
Want me to show you my right?
Bring it on
Chinian
Luye
Keep it civil
Aside from limiting my power
I'll cooperate fully
Letting you roam free?
Are you kidding?
Since when does the Guild need
to consider a suspect's feelings?
Leaving someone like him here, unrestricted
Puts everyone at risk
Then he stays with me
OK
What?
Relax
I won't let him out of my sight
Wuxian
You're not allowed to contact anyone
Is that really necessary?
Xiaohei, stay with your Shijie for now
I don't want to
I want to be with Shifu
Don't worry, nothing will happen to Shifu
I'm worried someone
might try to hurt your Shijie
You must protect her
I'm entrusting her to you
Take good care of him
And don't do anything reckless
Worry about yourself
OK
Shifu
Let me go
I want to be with Shifu
Where has Shifu been lately?
Do you trust Shifu?
Of course
I'm going to find the real culprit
How?
Where did Shifu go these past few days?
He's just been at home
Just at home?
When was the last time you went out?
Over ten days ago
We went to the amusement park in the city
Do you know anyone in the Guild?
Jiulao and Ruoshui
I'll take you to them now
Why?
There's something I need to take care of
You stay with them for a few days
No
I'm going with you
I won't hold you back
I'm also Shifu's disciple
Fine. But if you can't
keep up, I won't wait
So where are we going?
Liu Shi Guild. The crime scene
But everyone has already checked that place
What are we trying to find there?
Traces of Ling Power
Can't others see that too?
They can
But this
This is my specialty
Lord Luye, where to?
Do I report to you now?
That's not what I meant
But you're Lord Wuxian's disciple
We have to monitor your whereabouts for now
Ridiculous
Since when does the Guild have such rules?
Get out of my way
Do not follow me
Enforcers are allowed to
eliminate stalkers on the spot
So arrogant
Elder, what should we do?
Follow her
She's just bluffing
It's snowing
Lord Luye
I'm just looking around
It's warmer this way
Who's that?
Ming Wang
Just like Lao Jun
She's one of the Guild's founders
Was the Portal destroyed?
Yes
Not sure if it was sabotage or
just collateral from the attack
How many people have used the Portal
around the time of the attack?
We were the first to arrive
once repairs were done
After that, the captain
took over the Portal
And everyone who passed through that day
Was marked as a suspect
Do you have the teleportation records?
Yes
Captain
Shifu
This is your uncle master
I've heard so much about you
Hello
My name is Xiaohei
Hello, Shishu Xiaohei
Any progress?
I'm not allowed to discuss
the case with you, Shifu
Fine. Any trouble with
tracing the Ruomu Wood?
No
Good
If you had trouble tracking the Ruomu Wood
Then you're no disciple of mine
I won't let that happen
You guys go ahead
I'll just have a look around
I've heard about your abilities
Can you get that record?
Do we need that?
Yes
Here you are
Interesting
Put it back
Lord Wuxian
Please don't leave this property
Thanks for bringing me here
Not too shabby
This isn't what I imagined
your house would look like
Come in
I don't know how to play
I'll show you
Easy
Hold it like this
This controls the direction
B is for jumping
A is for hitting
And don't run into monsters
Do you think it's me?
The strong are always envied and resented
I totally relate
But whoever it is...
It's someone inside the Guild
That's for sure
If it is you
I'm here
And if it's not you
We're here together
What could go wrong?
Luo
Hurry up!
What do you need, my lord?
Wanna play?
Uh... maybe next time?
Yue Dong Guild
He Hai Guild
What are we looking for?
If you're staying with me, no questions
Huang He Guild
Dong Qiao Guild
Rong Cheng Guild
Han Mu Guild
Hua Jian Guild
Mao Zhu Guild
Weren't we just here?
Are you hungry?
Just make do for now
This is make do?
You and Shifu
What do you guys usually eat?
Whatever Shifu cooks
Is that even edible?
It's actually not bad lately
No way
They were just here
Why did they come back so soon?
They must've found something
Kongkong
What's Lord Luye doing here?
Grabing a meal
Just for a meal?
And some soup
Did she go anywhere
else, or did anything else?
That's odd
They came all the way
back, just for a meal?
Hey
Everyone knows Yue Dong Guild
serves the best food in all the Guilds
Many Enforcers travel here just
for our cooking! Don't you know?
Okay, okay, got it
You done? Let's go
It's really good
Where did Lord Luye just teleport to?
Destination
Dong Qiao Guild
Dong Qiao
Weren't they just th...
Shoot!
Dong Qiao Guild!
We lost them!
I thought you'd come
up with something smart
Who's there?
It's me
I have an urgent mission.
The maintenance fee is on me
Pull every second of security
footage and then seal them all
Especially from yesterday
Miss even one tape...
and I'll hold you personally responsible
Yes, Lord Luye
We've been here
Is there any clue here?
Don't worry
They won't find me for another day
And within this day
I'll catch the real culprit
That means you'll be arrested tomorrow
And?
Captain
We found it
Good work. I'm on my way
Check this out
The Ruomu Wood was split into three parts
3 parts?
One part went this way
And another this way
On those two routes, they didn't carry much
Cutting the Ruomu Wood is no easy task
Huohua, Aji
I'm leaving this to you two
Set the Ling Detector to 13.89
Yes, captain
The main chunk of the
Ruomu Wood went this way
We are on it
The aircraft it's on is a TM-203 model
Already located
Military-grade
That narrows things down
Don't lose it
Aggro the mobs
It went your way
Look out
You're picking it up fast
By the way
Has Xiaohei's Ling Zhi Realm stabilized?
It's getting there
In another year or two
He'll be able to master it
That fast?
He must be working hard
Yes
If it goes out of control,
it can be very dangerous
Better to stabilize it as soon as possible
Lord Wuxian
Lord Luye just destroyed
the Portal at Dong Qiao Guild
Now they are expressing
more concerns about you
I knew she wasn't gonna sit still
What's wrong?
The second he left the Guild
He started clearing his
own Ling Power traces
Did a pretty good job too
So what now?
What's this?
Residual Ling Power
seeps into the environment
Even the best can't erase everything
Looks the same to me
Not to me. Everyone's Ling is unique
He has the ability to mask his Ling
But under scrutiny, the truth shows
What are they doing?
Your disciple didn't
investigate this place?
This Branch Guild is not in their records
Why not?
Someone has tampered with it
It makes sense
Only someone inside the
Guild could frame Shifu like this
So it was you
You found him?
That way
Uber?
This is not u...
Robber!
We can't steal!
I'm only borrowing
You gotta ask for permission first!
Coming or not?
I'm leaving
Shifu told me to watch you
He's just taking a nap
Told you we should've grounded Luye too
But you are so worried
about rules, procedures
Now look
We can't formally restrict her
But if she goes rogue
That's good
Besides, didn't you
have someone tailing her?
You're playing favorites
This Wuxian
This Human mascot of yours
There are more Humans
than Spirits in the Guild now
Coexisting with Humans, that's the future
Without Humans
Life would be so boring
Spirits ruling Humans
Isn't that coexistence as well?
We're not trying to wipe them all out
Every country where
Spirits rule over Humans
They are all decades behind the times
You think they're behind?
Aren't they?
Humanity has blazed a
new trail through technology
The Guild is not left behind
Because we have actively participated in it
True coexistence requires
the strong to take the initiative
There was a time
When tigers were stronger than Humans
But now
Humans already can kill most Spirits
with conventional firearms
Give it a few more decades
Do you think Spirits will
still be stronger ones?
If we leave the chances to
Humans and pray for their mercy
Spirits
Will be zoo animals just like tigers
We are making progress too
But are we developing faster than Humans?
Humans might never be
able to develop weapons
That can kill true strong ones like us
But if one day
All the other Spirits are eliminated
Will you avenge them?
Or continue to coexist with Humans?
If a war between Humans
and Spirits is inevitable
I'd rather it be now
Regarding those Humans
developing anti-Spirit weapons
We must show strengths
and take appropriate measures
They will face the punishment they deserve
But not all Humans are enemies to Spirits
The Guild today
Is more like a force in the Human world
A superpower among nations
So in order to protect our diplomatic image
We can't even touch an Enforcer
just because he's Human?
Wuxian didn't have to be an Enforcer
It was his choice
Don't tell me you see
him just as an Enforcer
If he chose this path
Then that's what he is
Wuxian is much stronger than you
What?
We found the Human gang
that attacked Liu Shi Guild
Where?
Quarento
And the Ruomu Wood?
Moved
We're tracking it
You know what to do
The management wants a live one
Got it
What about Elder Jingyi?
She said
She wants no part of this
Why?
She doesn't think it was Wuxian
That's not fair
I don't want to be involved either
You have to be
If we all back off
He'll have to face Elder Chi alone
The Liu Shi Guild incident
Caused more frictions than expected
Come on
Who do you think you are?
Just leave them
Stop it
Come on
You think you're strong?
I'll show you what's what
What's the point of bullying us?
If you've got guts, challenge Wuxian
Yeah
He'll get his turn, after I'm done with you
Elder
You were saying?
The nerve of you
Throwing punches right inside the Guild?
Have you all forgotten the rules?
Elder
Look what Humans did
You want us to keep swallowing this?
Was it them who did it?
Xiaofeng
Yes
Heal them
Yes, Elder
You think Spirits are
noble and Humans are lowly
Look at what you've done
How is that any different from
humans that you hate so much?
Now go. Claim your punishment
If this happens again
I'll make sure the consequences are severe
He's stopped masking his traces
Probably feels safe now
Hey
That's all you've got?
Put these in your Cosmic Pouch
Quite heavy
Can you keep up now?
Of course
Don't worry about me
OK
Where did she go?
Cheap tricks, can't fool me
He thinks he's completely safe now
Imprisoned Wuxian, have you lost your mind?
Jiulao
Did you fill in your eyebrows?
Don't bother
Are you getting senile?
Have you forgotten what
Wuxian means to this Guild?
Everyone saw the evidence
I can't just turn a blind eye
That's Wuxian you're talking about
Exactly. Which is why I
need to be even more cautious
I am the Guild Lord
If I start bending rules
How do I expect anyone to respect the Guild
and follow the rules?
Are you accusing me of being partial?
Yes, I am
I want to see him
No way
No one sees him until we reach a conclusion
I will see him
You just pretend I'm not here
Watch him
I couldn't stop him even if I tried
Lord Pan
Help me with something
Why is it so small?
The main part of the
base is right under our feet
I can sense the Ruomu Wood
You two, retrieve it
Zhiqing, D, with me
Yes, sir
Where's your boss?
You are no match for Dasong
Elder. We found the Ruomu Wood
Take it back. Let's go
Got you
Where am I?
How's it going?
He did drop his guard and
stopped masking himself
But there are too many Ling in crowds
It's harder to pinpoint his
And we don't know what he looks like
You have to kick him that far?
This way
Stop shifting forms
You little brat
I'll put you in your place
Stop
I said, stop
Stop it
Stop!
Stop beating
Look who I am
Stop!
I'm Wuxian, Xiaohei! Look closely
I am your Shifu!
Your Shifu, Wuxian
Xiaohei!
I'm your
Shifu!
Not bad
Nihuang
I know who you are
You're no match for Dasong
Who else was there that day?
Fine
Once we are back at the Guild
Plenty of ways to make you talk
Why don't you just put
him in the Cosmic Pouch?
Can't. A Fixed Space Cage,
and anything it contains
Can't go into the Cosmic Pouch
You didn't know that?
Now that we've got him
Shifu will be okay, right?
It's not that simple
Let's take him back first
You're progressing too fast
Are you guys having a good time
while the Guild's falling apart?
Are you having a bad time?
You know what I mean
Do I?
Don't worry
Everything's fine
You're not mad?
What's there to be mad about?
I got special treatment
Clearly someone's trying to tie your hands
with outdated rules
People are already digging into it
All I can do is wait
You ba...
What?
Two pieces of news
Good news first:
Luye caught the guy pretending to be you
They're coming back tomorrow
And the bad news is
At the mercenary base, where
the stolen Ruomu Wood was found
The security footage and the Ling Detector
Both cofirm that you were there
Where?
Quarento
Where is that?
How should I know?
What?
The Portal is still down?
We're doing everything
we can. It can't go any faster
You tore down the wall, Lord Luye
How much longer for the repairs?
Three more days
And the security footage?
What did they find?
A colleague got back
from the Portal yesterday
And we confirmed
He wasn't here yesterday
You reported it?
Of course
Footage and witness accounts,
everything's backed up and submitted
Good
I requisitioned seven cars, by the way
Took pictures of the plates
If there are any follow-up
issues, you guys handle it
Understood
Can I add you?
Which Guild is closest to here?
Feng Ling Guild
2,300 kilometers
Fastest way there?
There's a flight tomorrow
morning, in the city
You don't have jets here?
No
What would we need jets for?
For emergencies?
That's what the Portal's for
Book me two tickets
Well...
Actually, the Guild actually
issued a warrant for you
I'm booking the tickets
just so we can get back
Or you can take me back
I wouldn't dare
Then book the tickets
Right away
You ever been on a plane?
Not yet
Have you seen one?
They are in the sky every day
Of course I've seen one
Don't treat me like a kid
Alright
Let's go
Get a good night's sleep
We leave first thing in the morning
What's the best hotel around here?
We've got rooms just upstairs at the Guild
I said, the best hotel
Where is it?
This place is huge!
It's all ours?
Go take a bath
You can use the bathroom
and bedroom over there
OK
You eating?
Of course
Shower first
OK
Mmm... Delicious
This is so good!
You like it? We can order more
Shijie is the best
You are just like Shifu
What are you talking about?
We're nothing alike
You seem really annoying at first,
but you're both really kind
Is that supposed to be a compliment?
Why don't you live with Shifu?
I'm not a kid
Why would I live with Shifu?
I'll live with Shifu forever
So you are a kid
Besides, I don't like living among Humans
Why not?
I don't feel free
In the Guild, I can be myself
No hiding, no pretending
That's a good point
That bracelet
Is it your special metal?
I've never seen you use it
This?
Shifu gave it to me.
It suppresses my spatial manipulation power
To suppress?
Yes
Because I can't control it very well yet
Shifu said not to use
my spatial power for now
So it's a limiter. To stabilize the power
Can I come visit you in the future, Shijie?
Of course
I'll show you around. We'll
eat all kinds of amazing food
You're my favorite person in the world
What about Shifu?
Shifu is my first favorite
Do you even know what "favorite" means?
Shijie
How did you and Shifu meet?
We bumped into each other on the street
Shijie
How did you and Shifu meet?
Let's go
This thing's huge! How can it be this big?
Didn't you say you've seen planes before?
Only the tiny ones, in the sky
Even the plane in amusement
park was much smaller than this
Hi
What a coincidence
Lord Luye
Let's not cause a scene here
We'll talk at the Guild
OK
Let's go
By the way
What are your names?
My name is A
I am B
Who gave you those names?
Elder Chi
Next time you pick a boss,
maybe choose someone more educated
Should we report that to Shifu too?
You have a death wish?
Welcome aboard, little one!
Hello
Where's your seat?
9H, 9K
You sit here
Um
It's so high
Let's check the waypoints
Yes, captain
On it! I'm doing it
Like right now!
Hi, little one
Thanks
Do you need anything?
Here you go
Are you OK?
Can you still find it?
The Ruomu Wood's traces
are very distinct to us Spirits
It's nearly impossible not to find it
So I've been thinking...
Maybe Humans are being used
I get what you're saying
As long as you return all the Ruomu Wood
And hand over who's behind the attack
We can let all of this go
The Guild doesn't oppose
Humans researching Lingzhi
However
This is not how the
research will be conducted
We'll share this information
with all nations today
I'll get back to you as soon as I can
Good
Sorry for the trouble
Pan
You should stop by more
often, even without business
I will
Have a good trip, sir
Bye
So this is the famous Yao Ling Guild
It is indeed
You'll need to learn how to collaborate
Was he threatening us?
Don't overthink it
Over the past few decades
Whenever conflicts arose
between the Guild and Humans
They never acted recklessly
They always presented
clear chains of evidence
And cooperated through
repeated investigations
There hasn't been a breach of trust yet
Although they are powerful
They're not arrogant
Their goodwill
Can we count on it?
Trust has to go both ways
We share the same goal
Peaceful coexistence. Mutual growth
If I put it in perspective
They might be the most
reasonable superpower
That we had to deal with
Let's send a notice to all nations
This is no small matter
Will anyone respond?
You think
He is expecting us to give answers?
What else?
He just wanted to spread
the word through us
Those people outside, are they yours?
No
Watch out
The plane is hitting turbulence.
Please stay calm and fasten your seatbelts
Put on oxygen masks, NOW!
What's happening?!
I'll put it in manual
Put on your oxygen mask!
I have it under control
I got you!
Let's go
You can't get rid of her this easily
Don't worry, everything's
going according to plan
What do we do?
It's working
The plane is... flying itself!
What's going on?!
Don't move
The plane has three
minutes of flight left, at most
You two stabilize the aircraft
Glide as far as you can
Who are you?
She's right
We need an emergency landing site, now!
Wait for my instructions
Emergency landing? Are you insane?!
There's nothing but mountains here!
One mistake and we're all dead!
Then you'll just have to trust me
What?
A, B
What kind of abilities do you have?
Earth manipulation abilities
Useless
What?
Gather everyone in the
center cabin. I'll tell you the plan
Copy that
Can you fly?
Yeah
Are you an owl?
Everyone move to the center cabin
The plane is stable now
Folks in the back, keep moving
No need to panic. We have time
Still two minutes before we crash
Your way to calm people down
What now?
Cliff up ahead. Turn the
aircraft 30 degrees to the right
There's no other way
Almost done on our side
Then hurry up and take your positions
Here we go
Get ready
We are in position
Mom, I need to go to the bathroom!
Xiaohei
That was close
I thought we were gonna die
They all got away
What now?
Don't worry
Once I've known someone's
Ling, I can always find them
Can you still walk?
Good, take care then
Let's go
What's wrong?
You
Yesterday, you asked
the Guild to book our tickets
You wanted them to find us, didn't you?
Haha
Someone's brain's working today
What about Nihuang?
You knew he'd get rescued?
Yep
Destroying the Portal
also part of the plan?
Why?
We've caught him
Why not just take him back?
He is too weak
To be the mastermind behind all this
But he can prove Shifu's innocence
I told you
Shifu is safe
What I'm after, is the full truth
Catching one pawn isn't enough
Then why didn't we just take a car?
Because that would be suspicious
And the target wouldn't
be easy enough for them
If we drove, they might not have shown up
What if your plan failed?
Then we'd turn him in
Still a win
I was asking
What if all those people died?
But they didn't
That was pure luck!
You're right
But when an Enforcer is on a mission
Even your own life becomes
a secondary concern
Who cares about the Humans?
You're a bad person!
I'm not a Human
I'm a Spirit Enforcer
If you had to choose
between Shifu's life and theirs
Which would you choose?
Right now, it's not like what you said
No... it's worse right now
You still don't get it
If we can't find the real
culprit behind all this
War will be inevitable
If we hesitate
We save no one
Let's go
No
Seriously?
I'm not going
What did we find?
Mt. Yinhan Base
The Ruomu Wood is 500
meters beneath the surface
The land belongs to Sioranmo.
They have no diplomatic relations with us
Which means no Branch
Guilds here, no Portals
Nearest Guild?
Over 5,000 kilometers away
Situation around this base?
High-point sentries everywhere
Except here, the only blind spot
Don't underestimate Human surveillance
We're very careful
Build a temporary Portal
Keep the others on standby
Yes, sir
No Spirits here?
Hardly any
This land has weak Ling Power
And about three hundred years ago
Humans killed all the
Spirits who once lived here
It's up to you now
I'll do my best
Humans are coming so fast
Because they're everywhere
Is it true that when an
Enforcer is on a mission
They don't care about Human lives?
It depends
On a difficult mission
Too much emotional weight means failure
Even including deaths
So sometimes
Being detached helps minimize casualties
But she did it on purpose
She also tried her best to save them
That's just what she's supposed to do
Lord Luye
Had another Shifu
Before meeting Lord Wuxian
At that time
Their homeland became a Human battlefield
Lord Wuxian saved her life there
But her Shifu then
Didn't make it
Everyone she knew, all the Spirits
They died
Shijie
How did you and Shifu meet?
We bumped into each other on the street
So I don't think it's
her job to save Humans
If it were me, I couldn't do it
I don't agree with what she did
But I should be with her now
Go find her
We're fine
Be careful
Your Shijie
Is just like you
She's one of Shifu's most important family
You'll like her
But she's such a jerk!
Cang Nan Guild
Lord Haoke
There's a special order today
The Grand Plaza is closed
I'm here to execute that order
Yes, sir
Make way! Make way!
Don't push. You can't get in
I have an emergency!
They said for emergencies,
go to the new district
Then what are you doing here?
Don't wanna miss the fun
What's going on?
No clue
They just kicked me out
But all the big names are inside
Lord Tianxin, are you not going?
My abilities aren't suited for this one
Then I'm off
Break a leg
Shui
Jingyun, everyone's
talking about you two lately
Still so quiet, though
So many seniors
How many Enforcers are
sent to carry out the mission?
Thirty first-level Enforcers
That's enough to level a country
This is war
It's been years since a battle this big
Told you, Humans can't be trusted
Dasong was not an easy one to take out.
Don't underestimate them
Honestly, I don't believe it
I'll see for myself
Shouldn't we try talking to them first?
They didn't talk before they attacked
The Guild Lord gave the green light?
If he puts up with
outright provoke like this
He doesn't deserve to be the Guild Lord
Some battles...
Must be fought
Tell me about it
Pair of Aces
Your turn
Don't rush
Luo
Lord Wuxian
There are many Enforcers
gathering at the Portal
What's going on?
Why are you looking at
me like that? Just tell him
Okay
They've located the Ruomu Wood
Deploying so many Enforcers
Where is it?
Um
Where are you going?
That many Enforcers are
not for a retrieval mission
It's for war
You'll only complicate things if you go
I can execute this mission
You
Can't go
I have to
You kidding?
Get out
Maybe this is what they
want, keeping me here
Come on, you'll trash the whole place
Where are we on schedule?
Ten minutes out
Good
They're on the move
Maintain concealment
Avoid direct conflict
Yes, sir
Two minutes out
Break concealment
Protect the Portal
Yes, sir
The enemy's attacking the Portal!
Get ready
Wuxian?
Is he going too?
No way. They're attacking a Human base
What are you doing here?
I'm here to execute the mission
You really want to prove
your own guilt, Wuxian?
Suits me just fine
We must retrieve the Ruomu Wood
But not like this
I'll go
What did you do to Nezha?
What could he possibly do to me?
This is how you keep an eye on a suspect?
I see no reason why he shouldn't go
If anything goes wrong,
I'll clean up the mess
Is he saying he can handle this alone?
Interesting
Elder, the Portal is now linked
The other side is under attack
If you get in my way,
I'll treat you as an enemy
Let's go
Wuxian
Haoke, Mangyan
You go first
Protect the Portal
Why should I take orders from you?
We're through!
Take him down!
Damn it! Why can't I go back?
The temporary Portal is only one-way
It'll reverse after the mission's completed
I can't handle that
Call Mangyan
That's yours now
Come here, everyone!
Smash it
Tired of running?
I heard there's only one
way to escape from you
That is, to kill you
Sounds about right
But no one has succeeded yet
This kind of place is my home ground
What's your gameplan?
That's
That's Metal Severing Circle!
Now you can't control any metal
Couldn't you just find
a spot without metal?
Why go through all this trouble?
You'll regret that mouth of yours
Now your special metal is useless
Setting this up wasn't easy
It took thirteen spell
circles of different heights
Stop babbling! Come help us!
That's not good
She's trying to breach the Circle
She's too fast
I can't catch up with her!
Dasong's Liushi Shield
You finally showed up
Lord Lingyao
How'd you know it's me?
No Portal warning
The teleportation records
were tampered with
Someone strong enough to defeat Dasong
Who also knows Shifu well
You were a suspect from the beginning
Liu Shi Guild had traces of your Ling
But you visit there often
So it couldn't be evidence
But now that you're here
You think I won't recognize your Ling?
You're smarter than I thought
Didn't you always support
the Human-Spirit alliance?
Why?
It's a bit of a cliché
But things have changed
I've witnessed enough
escalating wars Humans started
Plus, the existence of
super Humans like Wuxian
Don't get me wrong, I like him
But he's terrifying
Luye
You and I shouldn't be fighting
The future of Spirits
That's what we should care about
Don't you hate Humans?
I hate war more
This is the war to stop all wars
Is that so?
Why kill Dasong?
He didn't want to join us
There was no other way
If you stop me
His death would be for nothing
The price has been paid
Let's not waste their sacrifice
Waste
Their sacrifice?
Kill her
Ignore him!
We can also enter the portal from its back!
Aren't you going to join them?
If I join the fight, I'd
be beating you guys
What a huge gap between us
You stay put
Wuxian, stop
What?
Lao Jun's Qiongyuan Shield
So you do have something up your sleeve
One must have some way to save one's hide
We'll see if your
reinforcements arrive first
Or if your shield breaks first
You're already out of options
Someone breached the barrier!
The Guild's team
already arrived? That fast?
It's that little cat
Kill him
Yes, sir
Careful. He's stronger than he looks
How strong can a kitten be?
Shijie
Are you alright?
What are you doing here?
I came to protect you
You're just in the way
You little brat!
See?
You dragged an innocent child into this
Elder Lingyao
Careful
He's the one behind all of this
What now?
The Qiongyuan Shield can't
cover two people at the same time
There're Metal Severing Circles
So no metal manipulation
abilities will work in here
We must break it
Otherwise, we don't stand a chance
Follow me closely
Don't fall out of step, okay?
Xiaohei!
I'll deal with Lingyao!
Did you not hear me?
Boss
We're on!
Spatial manipulation!
Told you
Kill Luye first
Seven circles left
We have to break them all
You cover me, I'll charge at full speed
Don't go head-to-head
with them. Stick close to me
Got it
Xiaohei!
I am relying on you this time
OK
Be careful
What's happening?
Earthquake?
No idea
It shouldn't be anything
too serious, right?
These two are just unreal
Aren't you taking this too seriously?
How could I stand a chance if I didn't?
Should we alert the Elders?
Don't cause trouble
We can't afford to piss off either of them
Is there even a worse scenario than this?
This Portal is over a
thousand years old, you know
Enough!
You can go
If I can confirm you are the enemy
That's also a good thing
Thank you, Elder Chi
Then I'll follow him, just in case
What are you doing?!
What's keeping you so long?
Check fire! All units check fire!
Grand Shifu
Good work
Someone clean him up
The Ruomu Wood is beneath the base
Strong firepower down there
Well
You guys better just take each other down
OK
This way
Again?
How do we keep up with this?
Where's boss?
How should I know?
Split up. Cut him off
Yeah
Guilian!
How many's that?
You weren't counting either?
Shijie
Alright alright
Fine
I surrender
You're certainly Wuxian's discip...
My turn now
Did we bring enough backup?
Is he alive?
Not even a scratch
Do you wish Wuxian never existed?
This kind of question
We can't talk about
Though it's not that complicated
if we were determined to handle him
Just have to sacrifice a
few hundred Enforcers
Or a Nezha
Get lost
Return our Ruomu Wood
So you're the most
powerful one in the Guild
Nezha
Shijie
Stop
I'll live. Don't touch me
Oh
How did you find this place?
I put an iron ball on you, didn't I?
Brat
Your ability... it pairs well with Shifu's
Having you as a disciple
He must be happy
Yeah, he is
You alright?
You're not mad at me anymore?
I still am
What you did was wrong.
That's what bad people do
Were you able to take revenge?
The thing is, they all died
They also died in the war
And they didn't even know what it was for
Then you can't get your revenge, can you!
Calm down
I'm mad
Do you hate Humans?
I hate these Humans
But there are many I care about
Like who?
Uncle Tao, Uncle Li,
Grandpa Chen, Uncle Dai
Mumu, Anan, Pianpian, Taotao
Okay okay, who are all those people?
I used to like Elder Lingyao, too
Why would he do this?
The funny thing is
You can never tell who's wrong
Until the very end
If one day
Humans and Spirits go to war
Which side would you take?
I'll be on the right side
I'll be on the Spirit's side
It's Owlman!
And two Batmen!
Right!
You guys should rest
No, it's true!
There's a piece missing
From the Ruomu Wood we recovered
That proves I can hide the
traces of the Ruomu Wood
If I want to
Think of that missing piece
As a reminder always be prepared for danger
How did you convince the Humans?
Once you understand what they really want
It's easy
What were you thinking?
Same as you
Coexistence with Humans is only possible
If we rule them
We are nothing alike
Didn't you say it yourself?
If we let them keep advancing
their technology freely
It's only a matter of time
before they surpass the Guild
Therefore
I wanted to give the Guild
an excuse to attack, as a gift
We don't need this excuse
But will you tell them the truth?
You won't
So
You will thank me for this
Let's go
I'll reflect on this at Icecloud City
Maybe in a few decades,
we'll be able to tell who's right
You're not going to Icecloud City
No one will ever know where you are
So you are saying
Three nations are involved
Yes
In three days
I'll head to Morgan for...
Where's Wuxian?
Gone
No goodbye? That's rude
What was that?
I think he lost the game...
and now he wants a rematch
Shifu
Can I have one more ice cream today?
Just one?
Fine
Do you think the ice cream
from that shop is tasty?
I haven't tried it
If it's not tasty
Can I get another ice
cream on the way back?
No
Okay, but what if I give
you my ice cream if it's bad
And buy myself a new one?
Deal
I'm going!
Shijie
We're heading back now
OK
Bye
Shifu
Come visit me more often when you have time
Can we come often?
Certainly